They know about the Stouts!
他们知道关于Stout一家 (的事情) 了
-The jig is up!What are we gonna do?-Hey, get a hold of yourself.
-那个诡计被拆穿了  我们要做些什么啊-嘿  控制一下你自己
-What are you talking about?-I'm in big...
-你在说关于什么-我陷入大......
I'm in deep poopy-do!
我在深深的便便里  [我有大麻烦了]
Calm down. Calm down.
冷静下来   冷静下来
Don't get your fur in a bunch. All we need is a new plan.
别把你的毛 (纠) 成一团  [不必烦恼] 所有我们需要的是个新计划
We do what we should've done in the first place.
我们做我们 (早就) 应该做的一开始
We should scratch him out.
我们应该把他划掉 [我们应该除掉他]
Scratch him out?
把他除掉
But, Smokey! The police are involved.
但是 Smokey 警察 (已经) 介入了
I don't wanna get kicked out of my house.
我不想被踢出我的家
I’m not a street cat. I'm a house cat.
我不是一只街头 (野) 猫  我是家猫
I don't wanna lose my furry basket or my tinkle ball that I pushed across the floor with my nose!
我不想失去我的毛茸茸的 （睡）篮或我的叮当球 我（爱）推着滑过地板用我的鼻子
No, buddy, pull yourself together.
不  伙计  控制下你自己
It’s settled.
就这么决定了
Stuart Little gets scratched tonight.
Stuart Little会被除掉今晚